（救急車のサイレン）
（神崎）こら　手ぇどけろや　メガネ。
Hey. Keep yer paws offa my
get-well basket, four-eyes.
こいつは　オレの見舞いだろうが。
（姫川）ハァ？何　ちいせえこと
言ってんの　お前。→
What? How could you be so stingy...
バナナの１本くらい
いいだろうが。
Kanzaki Hajime
Himekawa Tatsuya
You could at least spare me a banana.
（神崎）あ？いいわけねえだろ。
どたまカチ割るぞ　ハゲ。
Huh? As if...
I'll crack your friggin' skull open, baldy.
ハゲてね～し。
よく見ろ　フッサフサだろうが。
I'm not bald. Look at my lovely do, buddy.
つ～か病院まで　そのクソ目障りなリーゼントしてんじゃね～よ。
Yeah, I am. And a Duck's Ass ain't
somethin' you wear in a hospital, idiot.
定規で測んぞ　コラ。
Don't you have any common sense?
（姫川）いくらだ？
（神崎）あぁ？
How much?
いくら出しゃ　このバナナ
くれんのかって聞いてんだよ。
I asked you how much for
you to give me a banana.
３００万。
3 million.
（姫川）ハァ！？ぼりすぎだろ
ふざけんなよ！！
Huh?!
That's extortion! Hell, no!
（神崎）
うるせ～！社長の息子が
セコイこと言ってんじゃねえよ。→
Shut it! The son of a company president
ain't got no right to complain!
つ～か　そもそも何で
てめ～と同じ病室？
（夏目）あらあら。
And why are we in the same
hospital room anyway?
Oh, my...
邦枝？
戻ってきたのか　あの女。
Kunieda?
That woman's back?
（城山）ええ。
昨日　北関東制圧を終えて。
Yes. She finished her takeover
of North Kanto yesterday.
また勢力
増えてるらしいっすよ～。
I hear she's even more powerful than ever.
ふん。所詮　女の集まりだろ？
ああ　石矢魔は獲れね～よ。
It's just a gaggle of girls in the end.
Yeah. She ain't takin' Ishiyama.
いやいや。実際
邦枝は　やりづれ～っすよ？
Now, now... Kunieda is no easy pickings.
つええし　人望は厚いし→
She's strong and has deep support.
なんせ１年にして　石矢魔女子を
まとめあげたカリスマだ。
She had the charisma to unify all the girls
at Ishiyama when she was just a first-year.
ククッ…確かにガチでやりゃ
テメーは勝てねえだろうな。
You got a point. If it got
serious, you couldn't beat her.
あ？オメーも１回やられてんだろ。知ってんぞ。
Huh? Did you forget the
time you got beat yourself?
いやあ　オレはほら
フェミニストだから。
I know about that.
That's just because I'm a feminist.
女相手に　本気は出せね～の。
I can't fight seriously against women.
ぬかせ。言いよって
ぶっとばされたって→
Nonsense.
The rumors all say you got
your ass handed to you.
もっぱらの噂だぜ。
ああ？
っだぁ　こら？
（夏目）ま　それはともかく…→
Oh, yeah?
Yeah!
Anyway, leaving that aside...
東条一派は　正直　石矢魔統一
なんて興味ないだろうし→
It doesn't seem like Toujou's group has any
interest in uniting Ishiyama at the moment.
こうなると　男鹿ちゃんに頑張ってもらっとくしかね～っすかね～。
I guess we're in good little
Oga-chan's hands for now...
（神崎）っざけんな！！
あんな１年坊に！
（姫川）治す！３日で治す！！
Screw that!
Anyone but that first year punk-ass...
I'll heal! I'll heal in 3 days!
ちょっとアンタ達　またケンカ！？
いい加減にしないと！
Hey, you two! Fighting again?
I told you to quit it!
楽しいな～。
夏目　お前…。
This is gonna be fun.
Natsume... You're such a...
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんなことから
赤ん坊を育てることになった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語＞
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
＜但し　その赤ん坊は
普通の赤ん坊ではなく→
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
魔王の子だったのです＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
Even The Demon Lord Makes his Park Debut
（男鹿父）
ほ～ら　おじいちゃんだぞ～。→
Look at me! It's Grampa!
いないいない　ばぁ～！
Peek-a-boo!
（男鹿母）ベルちゃん
あんまり笑わないわねえ。
Beel-chan doesn't smile that much.
（美咲）辰巳の顔ばっか見てりゃ
愛想もなくなるわよね～。
After staring at Tatsumi's face all the
time, his grumpiness must be contagious.
（男鹿）うっせ～な。
Would you quit it?
《どうすんだよ　これ…むしろ
でっかくなってるじゃねえかよ》
What am I gonna do about this?
It's even gotten bigger...
まあ　ヒルダちゃんも
あんまり笑わないしね～。
Actually, you don't smile
much either, Hilda-chan.
（ヒルダ）そうですか。
Is that so?
（ベル坊）ダ…。
く～　こうなったら
男の生き様　見せてやる～！
If that's the way it's going to be, I'll
show you what it means to be a man!
いいか　ベルちゃん！これが男だ！必殺スライディング土下座～！！
Look at this, Beel-chan! This is a man's
secret weapon, the sliding grovel!
ダァ…。
おお…。
ダ。
おっ！
おいおい～っ…。
そうだ　あんたたち
公園デビューしたらどう？
Oh, I know! Why don't you
take him for his Park Debut?
はぁ？
（美咲）あ　それいいじゃん。
Oh, that's a great idea!
同い年の友達とかいた方が
絶対いいって。
He should definitely make some
friends about the same age.
公園…デビュー？
Park debut?
（アランドロン）
＜公園デビュー…
俗に公園で遊ぶ子供と→
"Park Debut"
It is when one first joins the community
of children and their parents at the park.
その母親が形成する
コミュニティーに→
初めて参加することを指す。
なお　これに失敗すると…ツライ＞
And, if you screw it up...
...you'll never live it down.
情報交換とか相談とか　あと同年代の友達もできるし　大事なのよ～。
Swapping information, asking for advice...
Also, he can make friends near his own age!
It's very important, you know.
もっとも…あたしの
公園デビューはアンタのおかげで→
Of course, thanks to you, my
Park Debut was a giant failure.
大失敗だったけどね～。ハハハ…。
（美咲）わかった？
いでっ！
Get it now?
Ow!
ヒルダちゃんも　マカオから来て
まだ　お友達いないでしょう？→
And you don't have any friends since you
came from Macao alone, right, Hilda-chan?
行っておいでよ
ベルちゃん連れて　公園。
Go! Take Beel-chan to the park.
あら　いいわね。公園デビュー。行ってらっしゃいよ。
Ooh, sounds nice. A Park Debut! Have fun.
（美咲）行けよ！
ガ…グググ…！
Go!
いてて…くっそ～
な　なんだよ。
Shit...
What?
だぁ…。
デビューしてこい。
Make your debut.
はぁ？
公園デビューとやらが→
It seems this Park Debut is indispensable
for the young master's development.
坊っちゃまの発育には
不可欠らしい。
貴様　行ってこい。
おいおいおい…。
Take him, you bastard.
Hey, hold it right there.
お前は何で　こね～んだよ？
Why won't you go?
私は…。
I...
おっ？
姉が…。
Sister...
姉？お前
姉とかいたのか？
Sister?
You have a sister?
姉が　妹の旦那に手を出して
でもその男は　実は姉の元カレで→
She made a play for her
younger sister's husband...
But it turns out that he
used to be her boyfriend,
かと思えば妹は　もしかしたら→
then the little sister realized,
she might actually be in love
with her half-brother...
異母兄弟かもしれない相手に
ひかれていて…。
というのを見届けなければ
いけないのだ。今日の１時半から。
昼ドラかよ！
You see... I must watch this closely.
Starting at 1:30 PM.
A soap opera!?
（古市）で　何でオレが
呼び出されるわけ？
And? Why did you call me out here, exactly?
あ…？なんとなく。
なんとなくじゃね～だろ！！
Huh? 'Cause I felt like it.
You felt like what?!
ああ　何でこんな昼日中（ひるひなか）に
男と赤ん坊連れで公園なんぞに…。仕方ねえだろ！
Why do I have to take a baby to the park
with another guy in the middle of the day?
I had to, okay?
こいつのために　公園デビューとやらをしなきゃなんね～らしいんだから。
I gotta Park Debut him or somethin'...
公園デビュー？
Park Debut?
公園　奥様　若奥様
人妻　昼下がりの…→
Park... Mothers... Young mothers... Another
man's wife... In the early afternoon...
Thank you, Oga!
サンキュー男鹿！
やっぱり　お前は友達だ～！！
You are, and will always be, my friend!
じゃあオレ　１７歳で女子高生で
魔女かもしれない奥様と→
Now then, I have a rendezvous with a 17 year
old high school mother who just might be a witch!
ランデブーがあるんで！
ランラランラン…。
お　おい！
Hey!
んだよ　役に立たね～ヤツだなあ。
ベル坊…おっ？
God damn he's useless.
Baby Beel.
ほ～ら　ゆうか　高い高～い！
キャー！ハハ…。
Yuuka, upsy-daisy!
ベル坊？
だ！
Baby Beel?
ったく…しょうがねえなあ。
Fine, if you insist.
Take this!
そ～れ　高い　高～い！
Upsy-daisy!
ひょ～っ！
うん…
はっ！しまった！！
Crap!
１５メートル離れたら
オレ　即死だった～！！
If he's more than 15 meters
out, I'm a dead man!
≪でね　その不良はいつも赤ん坊をおんぶしてるらしいの≫
And that delinquent is always
carrying around a baby...
≪ああっ　それ私も聞いた。何故か
いつも裸の赤ん坊でしょ？≫
Oh, yes! I've heard this as well.
For some reason, the baby's
always naked, right?
裸？どうして？
知らないわよ。
Naked?
But, why?
How should I know?
虐待じゃない？
ほら　最近多いから…。
Isn't that child abuse?
It's been happening more and more lately.
え～　やだ　こわ～い。
あら！葵ちゃん　今日もお散歩？
偉いわねえ。
Frankly, it frightens me...
Oh, look!
Taking a walk again today, Aoi-chan?
You're such a good girl...
（邦枝）…どうも。
Hello.
誰？
ほら　５丁目の神社の娘さん。
へえ　若いわねえ。
Who's that?
She's the daughter of the
temple priest in 5th block...
My, she's young...
まだ１７ですって。
≪え～！？≫≪１７歳で？≫
≪信じらんない≫
Only 17 years old!
17 years old?!
I can't believe it!
≪まったく　最近の子は
どうなってんのかしらね～≫
Honestly, young people these days...
《聞こえてるっつの！だいたい
光太は　私の子供じゃなくて→
I can hear you, damn it!
Kouta isn't even my kid!
弟なんですけど》
He's my little brother!
あのですね～　この子は…。
Um, just so you know, he's not...
《はっ！？
ダー。
何？》
What the...
（邦枝）
《流れ星…いえ　あれは…→
A shooting star?
That's...
赤ん坊！？》
っだ～！！
A baby?!
どけ～っ！！
Outta my way!
あっ！
ああっ！！
っふう　危ねえ…
つい　うっかりやっちまった。
That was close.
I wasn't really thinking back there.
１５メートルまで
間一髪じゃねえか。
I was this close to 15 meters...
あ～！
高い高いも　命がけだぜ…
ん？
Upsy-Daisy's a game of life and death.
あ～　あの人あれじゃない？ほら　例の不良。
裸の赤ん坊！
That's him! That's the delinquent
the rumors are about.
The naked baby!
やっぱり虐待じゃないの？関わらない方がいいわよ。
赤ん坊　放り投げてたものね。
It's child abuse, definitely!
Better not get involved...
He totally just threw his baby.
ダー。
《これは…
公園デビューのチャンスか！？→
This is my chance to make my Park Debut!
う～む…ここは何とかして
印象を良くせねば…》
I have to do something to
make a good impression.
ベル坊　笑顔だ　笑顔。
ダ！
ああっ！
Baby Beel, smile.
あ　ど～も　はじめまして…
こいつ　ベル坊って言います。
Hello! Nice to meet you.
This little guy's Baby Beel...
よろしく。
キャーッ！！
Howdy.
あれ？
これじゃあ　ダメなのか？
Huh? That didn't work?
《ま　まさか　こいつ…》
W-Wait, could he be...
まだ愛想が足りねえかなあ？
ベル坊　もっと笑え。
だ！
Maybe we need to be more friendly...
Baby Beel, smile more.
いや～！
今日は　いい天気ですねえ。
What lovely weather we're having today!
ダーブー！
ひぃ～っ！
あれ？おっかしいなあ？
（邦枝）ちょ　ちょっと！
Huh, that's odd.
H-Hey...
あぁ？
おおっ！
オレと…付き合ってください。
Please, do it with me!
は…？
え　え～と…。
Uh...
《私　なんか今　告白されてる？》
Was I just confessed to?
い　いやだって
そんな　いきなり…。
But, I can't just, like that...
《真剣なまなざし…ん？》
He looks serious...
《子供　めっちゃにらんでる！》
The kid's totally glarin' at me!
あい…ビー！
あ　えと…てゆ～か　まだ
あなたのこと　よく知らないし…。
Um... I don't really know
anything about you...
ああ　オレも　あんたのこと
よく知らね～けど→
Yeah. And I don't know much about you.
そういうもんだろ？
That's... the point.
公園デビューって。
You know, the Park Debut thing.
は？
ん？
んん？
公園デビュー…。
公園デビュー。
Park Debut?
Park Debut.
うっ…。
ん？
付き合ってくださいって…
もしかして　そういう意味？
"Do it with me?"
Was that what you meant?
へ？
他にどんな意味が？
What else would it mean?
What a jerk...
（邦枝）《このヤロー！！》
そんなので公園デビューできるわけないでしょ。
You can't have a Park Debut like that!
いやだって　どうやりゃいいか
わかんねえし。
But I don't know what I should do!
ばか！！公園デビュー舐めてるの？
Idiot! Don't go thinking
a Park Debut is so easy!
素人が気軽に手を出していい
領域じゃないのよ！？
It's not something a novice
should approach lightly!
じゃあ　あんたは
できてんのか？公園デビュー。
So, you've done it? The Park Debut thing...
あ…あたしは
今日は　これから…。
Me? I... was planning to today.
つ…付き合うわよ　あんたに。
Sure, I'll go along with you!
You and me.
おっ　そりゃ助かる。
悪ぃな～。
Oh, that'll really help me out!
Sorry 'bout this.
《あたしだって　ずっと
話しかけられなかったなんて→
I can't tell him that I never
actually spoke with anybody yet...
今さら　言えない…でも→
But... Maybe I'll try using these notes.
使ってみるか　このメモ…》
まずは挨拶から…。
We'll start with the introduction.
ギャハハハ…。
（邦枝）…なしね。
Or not.
べビー用品など　共通の話題を
さりげなく持ち出す。
Casually bring up some mutual topic
of conversation, like baby supplies.
あ～　この　おむつと
おしゃぶりしかねぇぞ。
All I have are these
diapers and the pacifier.
えっ？それだけ！？じゃあ
しかたないから　それで…→
Oh? That's all?
Well, if that's all, it'll do.
で…それどこのメーカー？
オムティ。
W-What brand are those?
Daipies.
ええっ！？あの幻の
おむつと言われてる？…いける！！
The ones called the mystical diapers?!
We can do this!
（邦枝）このおむつ
例のオムティですって！？→
Did you just say those are the
"Diapies" everyone is talking about?
わぁ～　スゴ～い！！
Wow! Amazing!
オムティ！？
うっそ～！！
Daipies?
No way!
すっご～い！
どうやって買えたの？
Amazing! Where did you buy them from?
《やった　くいついた
くいついた！！》
All right! They're totally hooked in!
あ～　駅前のドラッグストアに行ったら
たまたま銀行強盗がいてよ→
You see, at the drug store in front of the
train station these bank robbers happened by...
なんだかんだで　全員しめたら
店長が残り一生分くれた。
After I put 'em all down, the manager
there gave me a life-time supply.
強盗…。
全員…。
しめた…。
Robbers?
All of them?
Put them down?
（邦枝）ああっ…。
え～っと…次は子供同士を
おもちゃなどで一緒に遊ばせて…。
Um, next...
Get the children to play together with a toy.
おもちゃ？
持って来てねぇぞ～…。
Toy? I didn't bring any.
えっ…私も今日は
持って来ていない…→
I didn't bring one either.
ああ…じゃあ　これも却下ね。
I guess that one won't work.
（アランドロン）お困りですね
ムッシュｅｔマドモアゼル。
Are we having a quandary
Monsieur et Mademoiselle?
おおっ　お前
どこから出て来た！？
What the hell are you here for?
ほっほっほっ…
困った人々を助けるの紳士の嗜み。
It is only chivalrous for a
gentleman to help those in need.
いや　だから…。
だ…誰！？
Uh, that's not what I meant.
Who is he?
あ～　これは　その～あれだ…
え～　ベル坊の…。
He's... You know... That.
Baby Beel's...
縁あって
お仕え申し上げております。→
I am related to the child,
and my name is Alaindelon.
アランドロンと申します。
以後よしなに。
At your service.
あ…はい。
あの…どうぞ　よしなに。
Right. Um...
At your service, too?
（アランドロン）ああ…ああっ…んん～。
（ママ達）うわ～っ！
さあ　よろしければ
この　おもちゃをお使い下さい。
Now, please use this toy, if you'd like.
（邦枝）あ…ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
あれ？この人
おもちゃなんて持ってたっけ…。
Wait, did he have a toy?
（邦枝）《うっわぁ…》
あ～あの…良かったら　この
おもちゃで一緒に遊びません？
If you'd like, why don't we let
them play with this toy together?
ああっ…！！（ママ達）きゃあ～…。
えっ！？
（ママ達）きゃ～っ！！
（邦枝）えっ？えっ？
（光太）ああっ～…。
何なんだろう…変な人達。
What is with these weird people?
ごめんね…
なんか上手くいかなか…った！！
Sorry. It doesn't look
like anything worked...
おもちゃより　もっと
大事なもんがあるんじゃね～のか。
Aren't we forgetting something
more important than toys?
あっ…。
But... We just met, and...
（邦枝）いいや…だって…そんな
いきなり…会ってというか→
I don't know much about you at all...
まだ　あなたのこと
よく知らないし…あの…→
Um, I...
その…あああ～…。
There! Baby Beel!
こうだ　ベル坊。
はっ！？
だっ！！
あ～うう～…。
ダー！！
Yeah, that's the way, Baby Beel!
よし　いいぞ　ベル坊！！
ふぁいっ！！
な…何やってんの？
いや　公園デビュー戦を…。
W-What are you doing?
You know... the Park Debut match?
I think you're confusing this with K-1...
Ｋ－１か
何かと勘違いしてる？
Hey, Kouta! Don't fight back!
ダァ～！！
（邦枝）ちょっと　光太も！！
応戦しない！
ダッ～！
お～…。
Do it, Baby Beel!
いけ　ベル坊！！
坊っちゃま～！
Master!
光太　がんばれ！！
Kouta, you can do it!
ビ～～！！
あっ…。
Baby Beel!
ああ～～！！
ベル坊～～！！
Weak.
《よわっ…》
（アランドロン）
あ～　坊っちゃまは男鹿殿に
くっついていないと→
Ah... When Master Beel isn't attached
to Oga, he becomes so weak!
非力でございますからね～。
It is unavoidable, I'm afraid.
いたしかたありませんね～。
Don't just blab on like
it's not your problem!
他人ごとみたいに
言ってんじゃねぇ！！
ぎゃああ～～…。
Don't cry, Baby Beel!
おわっ　泣くな　ベル坊！！
What's this? I sense that Furuichi-dono
is in trouble elsewhere!
おや…あちらの方から
古市殿が困っている気配…→
おっほっほっほっ…
困っている人を助けるのが→
It is only chivalrous for a
gentleman to help those in need.
紳士の嗜み。では！
ハッハッハッ…。
If you'll excuse me!
うわっ！
こら待て　オッサン！！
（アランドロン）ハッハッハッ…。
Hold it right there, big guy!
えっ！？
ああ…忘れておりました
男鹿殿。ああ～っ…→
I almost forgot, Oga-dono...
これを。さあ　ここを握って。
Here. Now, squeeze this part...
あん？
Nice and tight...
（アランドロン）ぎゅっと。
ぎゅっと？
Nice and tight.
（爆発音）
うっ！
...if you do that it'll
explode, so be careful.
すると…爆発しますので
お気をつけて　アッハハハ…。
That bastard...
あんの野郎～…あれ？
Huh?
Baby Beel?
ベル坊？
（邦枝）えっ　光太？
Kouta?
Crap!
やっべぇえ～～…。
You! Search over there!
お前　そこらへん探せ！
あっ…うん！
Right!
Man, where the hell did he go?
おいおいおい…
どこ行きやがった　あいつ！？
7.8 meters!
（アランドロン）７．８ｍでございます。
えっ！？
（アランドロン）１０．１ｍ離れて
まいりましたな→
10.1 meters.
Getting colder.
５．９ｍ　男鹿殿
いい感じでございます。
5.9 meters.
Oga-dono, that is the way.
（アランドロン）
６．４ｍ　ああっ…惜しい。
6.4 meters... Ah, so close!
（アランドロン）１４．６ｍ　大変大変
風前の灯でございます。
14.6 meters. Warning, warning! You're
a candle flickering in the wind!
くっ！！
（殴る音）
Shut the hell up!
うるせぇええ～～。
（アランドロン）ほ～っほっほっほっ…。
（ドスン！）
（アランドロン）ああ～…。
T-There you are!
あ…お前ら！
ダァ～　ブ～！！
あ～い！
What the hell have you been doing?
何やってんだよ…ったく
心配させやがって。
Makin' me worried like that...
だっ！！
（邦枝）見つかった！？あ…。
Did you find them?
Oh... He's not really such a bad guy.
《なんだ…
悪い奴じゃないじゃない》
Officer, he's over there!
（ママ）
おまわりさん！！こっちです。
This way!
こっち！！
早く早く！！
Hurry up!
Aoi-chan, are you okay?
葵ちゃん　大丈夫！？
H-Hold it...
（警官）ちょ…ちょっと　ちょっと。
That's him over there! A big guy
that was with him just split open!
あの男です！！ツレの大男が
カパ～って割れて！！
変なぬいぐるみが　うちの子を
丸呑みしょうとしたんです。
A strange doll tried to eat my baby alive!
Really?
本当なんですか？
そんな　何かの見間違いじゃ…。
I think your eyes must have
been playing tricks on you...
Of course not!
そんなわけないでしょ！→
I'll sue you for dereliction of duty!
職務怠慢で訴えるわよ！
Anyway, there's clear evidence of
child abuse right in front of you!
（ママ）とにかく　幼児虐待と脅迫の現行犯だから！
Crap, I don't get this...
《まいったな…
わけ分かんね～よ…今日は→
I wanted to get home early
and get to my video games...
もう帰ったら　そっこ～　ゲーム
やりたかったのによ～…おっ！？》
（警官）《おおっ　１００点！
こいつはラッキー！→
A perfect 10!
This is my lucky day!
Sometimes this thankless job has its perks.
Goin' along with those old broads ain't so bad!
いい役回りじゃん。正直
あんなオバサン達　相手じゃ→
テンション
あがんなかったんだよね～》
《フン…こいつだけか…→
He's alone?
面倒くさそ～な大男とやらは
いねぇみて～だし…》
That "big guy" they mentioned
don't seem to be around, lucky me.
んっ！？
You there, is it true that you scared
those women over there with something?
おい　君！
あそこの奥さん方を→
変なもので脅した
というのは　本当か？
それに　その子供
虐待だという話だが…→
And they also said something
about child abuse?
おっ…見たところ確かに
服も着せてないな。
Now that I look at him, he's
not wearing anything...
Oh, yeah? Don't screw with me, buddy.
なんだ　そりゃ。
ふざけんなよ　オッサン！→
If anything, I'm the one bein' abused by him!
むしろ
俺が虐待されてる方だっての。
チッ…。
Damn it, what's the punk
starin' right at me for?
《おいおい　何まっすぐ
見てんだよ　ドカスが！！→
All these damn delinquents in town...
街の不良ってとこか…まったく》
Let me teach you a thing
or two about being polite.
（警官）
口のきき方から教えてやる。→
I'd like you to come to the station for now.
とにかく　署まで来てもらおうか。ああ？
あっ！
W-Wait, please!
（邦枝）
ちょ…ちょっと待って下さい。
そんな　確かめもせずに…。
Without any proof...
Hey, why are you covering for him?
おいおい　何で
君が　かばっちゃうわけ？→
あっ…
なるほど　そういうことか。
I see. So that's it.
（邦枝）はぁ！？
You're the same as him.
（警官）
君も　こいつと同類ってわけだ。
あ～あ…幻滅（げんめつ）だな。→
Ah, there goes my fantasy... I had
hoped you'd be a better girl than that.
君は　もう少し
頭のいい子かと思ってたのに。
Oh, yeah?
（邦枝）はぁ…！？
Man, you human trash just go
stickin' together so soon...
（警官）
まったく…クズはクズ同士→
すぐ　くっつくんだよ　バカだから。で…君　いくつ？
How old are you?
17. And...?
１７ですけど…。
（警官）はあ～…もう少しさ～
男見る目持った方がいいよ→
You should really get better taste in guys.
Goin' out with a guy like
this is a total waste!
こんな奴と　くっついたって
どうしようもないでしょ～？→
Delinquents like him are society's
trash, and they always will be!
不良なんて　所詮
社会のゴミだからね～。
あ？
And anyway, he's got a bastard kid already!
（警官）
だいたい　そいつだって
ど～せ　出来ちゃったガキだろ。
If you brats keep raising more brats,
the country's in big trouble!
まったく　ガキがガキ育てて
この国の未来が不安になるよ。
That's my line!
（邦枝）
《それは…こっちのセリフよ！》
あっ！？
おおっ…エッ…！？
You bastard! You think
you'll get away with that?
（警官）
ああ…貴様…こんなことして→
ただですむと思ってんのか！？
これは立派な犯罪だぞ！！
That's a serious crime!
Assaulting a police officer!
公務執行妨害だ！！
ぶち込んでやる！！貴様→
I'll throw you in the slammer!
I'll lock you up and throw away the key!
絶対に留置場に
ぶち込んでやるからな～！！
（警官）うわ～！
Hey, look what we got here!
奇遇だな…。
なっ…何をする！？おろせ！
W-What are you gonna do?
Let me down!
I was also thinking about
slamming you into something.
あっ…。
俺も　ぶち込もうと
思ってたところだ…。
Gotta...
ゴミは…。
（警官）わあ～ああ～…。
...throw out the trash!
ゴミ箱へ！！
（警官）うわ～～っ！
（ママ達）あ…あ…。
Laters!
じゃあな！
ダブ！
≪あっ　逃げた！≫
≪待ちなさいよ～≫≪こら～≫
He ran away!
Get back here!
Why, you...
《私が殴ろうとしたのを
止めてくれた…？》
He stopped me from hitting him?
It couldn't be...
まさか…ね。
（邦枝）帰ろっか　光太。
（光太）あい。
Let's go home, Kouta.
あっ　名前
聞きそびれちゃった…。
I forgot to ask him his name...
Yo...
≪チェ～ス！≫
チェ～ス！
Yo...
チェス！
Welcome home, Madame Aoi.
（寧々）お帰りなさい。葵姐さん。
ただいま。
I have returned.
You went to the park in that outfit again?
（寧々）また　そんな格好で公園に？
Kunieda
（邦枝）しょうがないでしょ？→
I have no choice. You can't have
the leader of the Red Tails,
関東最強のレディース
烈怒帝瑠の総長が→
the strongest ladies of Kantou,
seen carrying around a child.
子守りしてるとこなんて
誰にも見せられないもの。
As expected of you, Madame.
（寧々）さすがです　姐さん。
Madame, it is time for the general meeting.
（寧々）
姐さん　そろそろ総会の時間です。
（邦枝）ええ。今　行く。
Yes. I'm coming now.
Violent
Anger
Empress
Lapis
Kunieda Aoi
Ishiyama's Queen has returned!
And I hear she's a real beauty!
Queen? You mean Ishiyama
wasn't an all-boys school?
Oga Tatsumi, prepare yourself.
Your evil ways end here!
It's Queen Kunieda!
Ooh, Baby Beel likes her!
Okay, then! She's your new
mother, starting today!
On the next Beelzebub: We met again.
Huh? You mean we met somewhere before?